# **Mark Tran**

5 Romulus Street , Robertson 4109 QLD 0424 975 095 an.k.tran@hotmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/an-tran-51034613a/

# Summary

Postgraduate student who has years of IT experience with exceptional skills in Analysis, Object Oriented Design, Development and Implementation and Testing of Web Applications. Competent in utilising of Open Source application to generate substantial savings.

#### Transferable Skills:

- · Strong communication skills,
- Technically proficient and highly adaptable.
- A team player
- · Agile problem solving,
- Enthusiastic and eager to learn,
- Reliable and trustworthy team member with creative ideas,
- Pay a lot of attention to task detail and guarantee high quality

# **Career Objective**

Learning new programming languages and technologies is what I am passionate about. I'm open for an opportunity to further explore my career as a software engineer.

# **Employment History**

### August 2017 - Present

### MCA - System Administrator Queensland Australia

- Deploys and Configures Infrastructure Solutions.
- NAS implementation.
- Proactively identify issues and take corrective actions as required to avoid system outages.
- Configure and management of quota/access policies.
- Monitoring and reporting of deployed infrastructure.
- Installation/ Upgrades of storage hardware/software/firmware

### June 2017 - July 2017

# M-Tax Accountant - Web Developer Queensland Australia

Website developer, Intranet site development - Update and mitigate old website to Wordpress. Devised and Implement and Intranet site displaying various type of important data in an effortless end user interface

- Actively participated in requirements gathering, analysis, design and testing phases.
- Implements Intranet site with Node.js, Express, MongoDB and React
- Perform the responsibilities of implementing and hosting of systems on a web server.

- Build custom Wordpress plugin.
- Prepare documentation and user's manual for the application.

### **Education**

### **Master of Information Technology**

Queensland University of Technology

Feb 2016 - June 2017 Brisbane Queensland Australia

#### **Bachelor of Informatics**

**Griffith University** 

Feb 2013 - Nov 2015 Brisbane Queensland Australia

### **Bachelor of Computing and Information Sciences**

Ho Chi Minh City University of Science

2009 - 2011 Ho Chi Minh City Viet Nam

# **Degree Related Projects**

### Java Compiler - Queensland University of Technology (Feb 2017 - June 2017)

- **Purpose**: This project was completed for the IFN660 Programming Language Theory subject, as part of QUT's Master of Information Technology program. Development Stack: gplex, ggpg, C#.
- **Description**: The program was developed to read program text and divide into tokens. The list of tokens then arranged in a tree-structure (called the syntax tree) that reflects the structure of the program. We then did type checking to determine if the program violates certain consistency requirements. Lastly the Java program was translated to a .NET Intermediate language. With the ability to learn fast I be able to translate all the theories into practical code for our team and also mentor other members with weak technical skills. As a result, we have received a distintion our project
- Github: https://github.com/hudson684/IFN660-T5J/tree/master/Project Folder

# **Technical Skills**

### **Programming Languages:**

- Python
- C/C++, C#, Objective C / Swift, PHP
- JavaScript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, SASS
- JSON, AJAX

### **Database**

- SQL Server
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL

#### Frameworks/ Platform:

- ReactJS, Redux, Angular JS 2/5
- Node.js, Express
- ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Core, Entity Framework
- Webpack, ES6
- RESTful
- Wordpress, Genesis Framework
- Xamarin Form
- Unity3D
- Docker

#### Administration

- Unix/Linux server
- Window Server 2012/2016
- Amazon AWS/ Azure

### **Soft Skills**

- Highly developed communication skills in both written and oral form.
- Technically proficient and highly adaptable,
- · Agile problem solving,
- Enthusiastic and eager to learn,
- Reliable and trustworthy team member with creative ideas,
- Pay a lot of attention to task detail and guarantee high quality.

# Languages

Vietnamese - Native

English - Fluent

# **Professional Memberships**

Australian Computer Society(ACS) - November 2017 - Present

# **Volunteer Work**

# Website Developer – Brisbane Artificial Intelligent Community (September 2017 - January 2018)

Working as Website Developer/ Website Administrator for Brisbane Artificial Intelligent Community

## Referees

Available on request